[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What is the only capable of true sustained flight?",
    "options": [
      "Flying Squirrel",
      "Sugar Glider",
      "Colugo"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Bat"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What is the official animal of Scotland?",
    "options": [
      "Scottish Terrier",
      "Highland Cow",
      "Red Deer"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Unicorn"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Which planet in our solar system spins on its side, relative to its orbit?",
    "options": [
      "Mars",
      "Venus",
      "Neptune"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Uranus"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What is the fear of long words called?",
    "options": [
      "Sesquipedalophobia",
      "Arachibutyrophobia",
      "Phobophobia"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Hippopotomonstrosesquippedaliophobia"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What is a group of flamingos called?",
    "options": [
      "A Murmuration",
      "A Gaggle",
      "A Parliament"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "A Flamboyance"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Which country is home to the most pyramids in the world?",
    "options": [
      "Egypt",
      "Mexico",
      "Peru"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Sudan"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "The electric chair was invented by a dentist named Alfred Southwick in which year?",
    "options": [
      "1845",
      "1902",
      "1928"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1881"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What is the only food that never spoils?",
    "options": [
      "Salt",
      "White Rice",
      "Vinegar"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Honey"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "How many hearts does an octopus have?",
    "options": [
      "One",
      "Two",
      "Four"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Three"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What is the chemical element with the symbol W?",
    "options": [
      "Water",
      "Platinum",
      "Iron"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Tungsten"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "The total length of all the veins, arteries, and capillaries in the human circulatory system is approximately how long?",
    "options": [
      "10,000 miles (16,000 km)",
      "30,000 miles (48,000 km)",
      "100,000 miles (160,000 km)"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "60,000 miles (96,000 km)"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "In which European country is it illegal to own only one guinea pig, as they are social animals that need companionship?",
    "options": [
      "Denmark",
      "Austria",
      "Norway"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Switzerland"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "Which famous artist requested to be buried in a Pringles can after he passed away?",
    "options": [
      "Andy Warhol",
      "Salvador Dalí",
      "Banksy"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Fredric Baur"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "How long is the shortest commercial flight in the world (between Westray and Papa Westray islands in Scotland)?",
    "options": [
      "5 minutes",
      "2 minutes",
      "30 seconds"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "90 seconds"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "Which one of these fruits/vegetables is actually a member of the rose family?",
    "options": [
      "Banana",
      "Orange",
      "Carrot"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Apple"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "What is the collective noun for a group of rhinoceroses?",
    "options": [
      "A Herd",
      "A Crash",
      "A Drove"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "A Stubbornness"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "What year was the widely accepted world's oldest piece of chewing gum found, which was an ancient piece of birch bark tar?",
    "options": [
      "1892",
      "1,500 BCE",
      "1950"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5,700 years ago"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "What does the # symbol, commonly called a hashtag or pound sign, officially called?",
    "options": [
      "Asterism",
      "Hashmark",
      "Number sign"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Octothorpe"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "In the 1980s, which celebrity was assigned a police officer to follow him when he was drinking to ensure he didn't fall on anyone?",
    "options": [
      "Michael Jordan",
      "Arnold Schwarzenegger",
      "Sylvester Stallone"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "André the Giant"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "What is the brightest star in the night sky (not including the Sun)?",
    "options": [
      "Alpha Centauri",
      "Polaris (The North Star)",
      "Betelgeuse"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Sirius"
  }
]